Yeah.
Viral told me you know the way to Meridian.
The carriage, a capital west will take you to it.
But their soldiers will stop you long before you get there.
They can try.
You know what I mean is there's a card of fort that guards the past between East and West.
Word is the card.
You have sealed the gate out of fear of the corrupted machines infesting our sacred land.
The card you call the placed a tower.
It's not far from the forsaken village.
See the secrecy?
Mhm.
Save these for the trail.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Grazer's can override them if I don't speak from here, you know?
Please.
Okay.
Scrappers happy to find salvages always.
Yes.
Mhm.
Mm hmm.
Just
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
No.
Hear, hear.
Okay.
Broadhead place.
Storage canister.
Porn's destroying.
This component disables the charge.
Attack.
Here we go again.
I don't know the details.
No.
Yeah.
See?
Okay.
There has been
Yeah,
Yeah.
What?
Oh,
mhm.
Yeah.
Mhm people.
Feet
mhm
e that.
Thank you.
Come on.
Yeah,
well,
okay.
Thank you.
Okay.
You gotta push weapons.
I think
Okay.
Help me.
Okay?
Yeah,
man.
Brother.
Everything
create.
I mean, yes.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Come on.
I don't have many shards when lives are on the line.
Your right Mind if I go looking for your friends?
So pay up or shut up.
But without these explosive arrows that we talked to shreds.
Not my problem.
Unless someone wants to pay me to pick up the pieces.
Help!
How could you be so cold?
Where I come from?
That's a compound.
See you around.
Sounds like you have friends in danger.
Employees, not friends Caravan on its way to trade with the bannock along a trail that swarms with machines, scrappers and long legs from what I hear.
But there have been stories of something worse.
Something that strikes with no warning.
Without explosive arrows, they won't stand much of a chance.
Why would they leave their best ammunition behind?
I don't know, Xavi.
The caravan boss isn't the sort of man to make mistakes.
They brought the crate hoping to catch them here on belly Got past the border before the commander sealed the gates.
For me to track them deeper into the wilds would be suicide, especially with those corrupted machines investing the land.
If I come across the caravan, I'll do what I can to help.
Well, that's more than any of the worthless bums hanging about this dump it offered.
Here, take the ammunition I stockpiled for the caravan you shorter needed on May the sun shine upon you.
Thank
just a moment, please.
Mhm.
Thank you.
I've hunted missions for so long.
I don't know what to think of a place where they're peaceful.
Curiosities,
lost something.
Products,
businesses, those permits.
Yeah.
Expected
status.
Should have gone out of it.
See,
You know
that's me.
Yeah.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
This is
mhm
disaster.
Yeah.
Mhm
over
scrappers collecting salvage.
Yeah.
Do you think?
Uh huh.
No.
What the Fuck?
Me?
Stop different,
right?
You?
Yeah.
It looks like liberal bods.
Men have to abandon some of their goods.
You?
Yeah,
this is
on a stand.
Gruber abouts Men must have killed his watchers.
E hope they haven't run into anything worse.
But the thing and
you there.
I hope you've come to help because we're getting slaughtered out here.
Luba vod sent me after you.
Oh, I see.
And did he happen to tell you why he packed as a creative Ridgewood instead of decent ammunition.
Three waves of watchers and scrappers so far and worse to come without that ammo.
We're good is dead.
He said you left the ammunition behind.
Then the old fool has gone cross eyed.
Every great we loaded.
I checked twice.
The glitch said ammunition.
But when we opened it, it was full of Ridgewood shafts and nothing.
But I have the ammunition with me.
Enough for everyone by the sun.
We might just stand a chance after all.
Hello, Arms Long.
Like approaching.
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you.
To arms to arms.
Come on, then.
Yeah,
Okay.
War
long leg weakness to shock concussions Sack Destroying this component Disables ranged sonic attacks and triggers A compressed air explosion.
Alarm signal antenna.
Destroying this component disables the ability to call in reinforcements.
Power cell shooting.
This component with shock arrows will trigger an explosion.
Electrifying Anything in the area wing destroying this component disables the charge.
Attack?
Yeah,
Okay.
E
No,
thank you.
Okay.
Well,
yeah,
I have to leave something else behind,
I think.
Yeah,
Yeah.
Thank you.
You fight well.
Loved lander.
I'm surprised Libya VOD was willing to pay for someone of your skill.
He didn't pay me.
Actually, I did this for free.
Never trust the card.
A merchant boss song cause they're gone.
What?
That's impossible.
Unless unless to read.
Took them.
When the first wave hit us, one of the men ran off Dory.
I thought he was a coward.
Turns out he's a thief to He couldn't have gotten far true.
But we're in no shape to go after him.
Then I'll get him for you.
But this time I get paid quick learner, Right.
Fine.
Bring those song cores back and you've got a deal.
Yeah,
yeah.
Hello?
Do read.
Who are you?
The caravan sent me Caravan.
What caravan?
The one you sabotaged.
You figured no explosive arrows meant no survivors.
No witnesses to your crime.
Look, stranger, I have debts.
If I don't pay, the Deisler's will gouge out my eyes.
Right, Right.
Oh, okay.
Stalker weakness to shock Dart gun Destroying this component disables the range Dart attack mine launcher Destroying this component disables the explosive mine attack Stealth generator.
Destroying this component disables the stealth ability.
Me?
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah
get his.
Yeah,
right.
Oh,
yeah.
Mhm.
Yeah.
Okay.
The caravan.
Did they live?
Yes.
I got to them in time.
Thank you.
As I turn
and embrace the sun
Hey, burn away
my sins.
What a waste.
At least he died better than he lived.
You mean
you?
You You
I mean
never know when I might need thes
You're back.
And with the sun cores I see.
And to read a stalker got him.
It wasn't pretty.
And you beat a stalker.
That's where the bonus.
Here, take my share.
You've earned it.
I'll see to the caravan from here.
I think the rest of the trip will go smoother.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Uh huh.
Thank you,
people.
Yeah.
Okay.
Mhm.
Thank you.
Yeah,
it can.
Yeah.
Well,
what do you think?
Okay.
Yeah,
yeah.
I'm not gonna be a problem overriding that Lance Horn
catching it, though.
Mhm.
Really?
Yeah.
Just take it.
All right.
Yeah,
right.
That's the money,
right?
Read.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yes.
Yeah.
Friends.
Okay.
I just
it
Thank you.
Yeah.
Six.
No room.
Somebody says something in my
eye.
No.
Yeah.
All right.
Thanks to the next house about?
Yeah.
Mhm.
Someone who lost someone close to
you so seriously.
Yeah.
Thank you.
And
okay, e know how to override a sawtooth if I can get in close.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Be fascinating if they weren't looking for me.
All right.
Yeah.
Drop.
Yeah,
Yeah.
Okay.
Huge.
It was Good morning.
I'm gonna need this.
Better,
E.
Yeah.
Let's see here.
Cash
e
from,
But
okay.
Okay.
Mhm.
I'd have to ditch something.
This is something that is not a problem, I suppose.
Just to stay out of the way from now.
Yeah,
Yeah.
Mhm.
Yeah,
Yeah.
Uh huh.
Sorry.
Should have brought a cards
E u.
Yeah,
just just
Just
mhm,
right?
Oh, boy,
you can't do that.
And mhm.
Okay,
good public.
Who's
mhm,
I think.
Uh huh.
From
Yeah.
Screams.
Right?
Yeah.
Oh,
yeah.
I don't know.
This just looks good.
Yeah.
Yeah,
This will do nicely.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Keep that for later.
I keep expecting,
right?
Yeah.
What is going on?
Okay.
Right.
Yeah,
right.
You see, an old gate broken long ago.
So this was the Nora border for the world's the car job.
Sorry.
Yeah.
And
the courage of fort looks solid.
A little too solid to talk about that
new passage West and no exceptions.
So long is corrupted machines proud of the valley.
Then why don't you do something about the infestation?
We have?
We sealed the border.
Fine.
I'll come back once I've destroyed all the corrupted.
Ha ha ha.
Uh, if you're serious, then may you go in, like, girl and the sun guide your arrows.
Yeah.